Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪Time rushes by, seasons change, autumn winds bring melancholy♪
♪يمر الوقت بسرعة، وتتغير الفصول، وتجلب رياح الخريف الكآبة♪
♪Scattered fragments can't piece together the memories of the past♪
♪الشظايا المتناثرة لا يمكنها تجميع ذكريات الماضي♪
♪The movie hasn't ended, tears glimmer in my eyes♪
♪الفيلم لم ينتهي بعد، والدموع تتلألأ في عيني♪
♪Sitting alone by the street, feeling lost and hesitant♪
♪أجلس وحدي في الشارع، أشعر بالضياع والتردد♪
♪Under the sycamore, let it drift, let it dance♪
♪تحت شجرة الجميز، دعها تنجرف، دعها ترقص♪
♪Whispering softly♪
♪همس بهدوء♪
♪The flowers that withered in my hand♪
♪الزهور التي ذبلت في يدي♪
♪Cannot call back the ones gone♪
♪لا أستطيع استدعاء من رحلوا♪
♪Under the sycamore, let it shatter, let it fade away♪
♪تحت شجرة الجميز، دعها تتحطم، دعها تتلاشى♪
♪Old stories like drifting dust♪
♪قصص قديمة مثل الغبار المنجرف♪
♪Letters too short for my long feelings, youth slips away♪
♪رسائل قصيرة جدًا بالنسبة لمشاعري الطويلة، الشباب يتلاشى♪
♪Farewell, my dear♪
♪ وداعا يا عزيزي ♪
♪Endless pain through day and night cycles♪
♪ألم لا ينتهي خلال دورات الليل والنهار♪
♪Longing and care♪
♪الشوق والرعاية♪
=Life Like=
=مثل الحياة=
=Episode 22=
=الحلقة 22=
Let's eat!
دعونا نأكل!
You made all of this?
أنت من صنعت كل هذا؟
Sure did.
بالتأكيد فعلت.
Try it and tell me what you think.
جربه وأخبرني ما رأيك.
It's really good.
إنه جيد حقا.
My foster mom taught me how to make the dishes.
علمتني أمي الحاضنة كيفية صنع الأطباق.
I grew up an orphan.
لقد نشأت يتيما.
My foster parents took me in.
لقد أخذني والداي بالتبني.
Eat while it's hot.
تناول الطعام وهو ساخن.
So,
لذا،
were they good to you?
هل كانوا جيدين معك؟
They were kind to me.
لقد كانوا لطيفين معي.
They treated me like their own daughter.
لقد عاملوني كأنني ابنتهم.
Even sent me to school.
حتى أرسلني إلى المدرسة.
If it weren't for them,
لو لم يكن لهم،
I never would've become
لم أكن لأصبح كذلك أبدًا
Zhou Musheng's junior.
صغار تشو موشينغ.
Is it good?
هل هو جيد؟
My foster mom used to tell me,
كانت أمي الحاضنة تقول لي دائمًا:
the way to a man's heart
الطريق إلى قلب الرجل
is through his stomach.
من خلال معدته.
You should work on your cooking a bit.
ينبغي عليك العمل على الطبخ الخاص بك قليلا.
Come on, don't tease her.
تعال، لا تضايقها.
I'll handle the cooking.
سأتولى الطبخ.
Can you even cook?
هل تستطيع الطبخ حتى؟
I'll learn.
سوف اتعلم.
It'll be edible.
سيكون صالحًا للأكل.
Definitely edible.
صالح للأكل بالتأكيد.
(Xu...)
(شو...)
(As long as Zhou Musheng truly cares for you,)
(طالما أن تشو موشينغ يهتم بك حقًا)
(I can be at peace.)
(أستطيع أن أكون في سلام.)
Dad.
أب.
This jade pendant is beautiful.
هذه القلادة اليشمية جميلة.
It's our family heirloom.
إنها إرث عائلتنا.
When you grow up and get married,
عندما تكبر وتتزوج،
I'll pass it down to you, alright?
سأمررها إليك، حسنًا؟
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Who bought these pomegranates?
من اشترى هذه الرمان؟
Man Li brought them.
لقد أحضرهم مان لي.
How does she know I love pomegranates?
كيف تعرف أنني أحب الرمان؟
She always brings them when she visits.
إنها تحضرهم دائمًا عندما تزورنا.
(My dear Xu,)
(عزيزتي شو)
(I wish I could tell you myself)
(أتمنى أن أستطيع أن أخبرك بنفسي)
(that I'm your sister.)
(أنني أختك.)
(But it's too late now.)
(ولكن الوقت قد فات الآن.)
Oh no!
أوه لا!
(When you open this letter,)
(عندما تفتح هذه الرسالة)
(I will already be gone.)
(سوف أكون قد ذهبت بالفعل.)
(I won't be able)
(لن أكون قادرا)
(to buy your favorite pomegranates anymore)
(لشراء الرمان المفضل لديك بعد الآن)
(or your candied hawthorns.)
(أو الزعرور المسكر الخاص بك.)
(Luckily, there's Zhou Musheng.)
(لحسن الحظ، هناك تشو موشينغ.)
(He can take care of you in my place.)
(إنه يستطيع أن يعتني بك في مكاني.)
(I often think back to the little moments from our childhood.)
(أفكر في كثير من الأحيان في اللحظات الصغيرة من طفولتنا.)
(I miss our father and mother.)
(أفتقد والدينا.)
(I hate Du Hongyue with all my heart.)
(أنا أكره دو هونغيو من كل قلبي.)
(For his own selfish gain,)
(من أجل مكاسبه الأنانية)
(he killed our father and mother.)
(قتل أبانا وأمنا)
(They died a brutal death.)
(ماتوا موتًا وحشيًا.)
(You and I were left alone and helpless.)
(لقد تركنا أنا وأنت وحدنا وعاجزين.)
(We had nowhere to go.)
(لم يكن لدينا مكان نذهب إليه.)
(When I think about it,)
(عندما أفكر في الأمر)
(I want nothing more than to crush him to dust.)
(لا أريد شيئًا أكثر من سحقه إلى غبار.)
(Don't blame me for leaving you behind.)
(لا تلومني على تركك خلفي.)
(If there is another life,)
(إذا كانت هناك حياة أخرى)
(I will be your older brother.)
(سوف أكون أخاك الأكبر.)
(You will be my little brother.)
(سوف تكون أخي الصغير.)
(I will use every ounce of strength to protect you.)
(سأستخدم كل ما أوتيت من قوة لحمايتك.)
(Take care.)
(يعتني.)
(Xu.)
(شو.)
(Your loving sister,)
(أختك المحبة)
(Zhen Yi.)
(تشن يي.)
You're awake.
أنت مستيقظ.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Let me go.
دعني أذهب.
You'll find out soon enough.
سوف تكتشف ذلك قريبا بما فيه الكفاية.
You're crazy.
أنت مجنون.
Let me go now!
دعني أذهب الآن!
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
You've really lost your mind.
لقد فقدت عقلك حقا.
Let me go!
دعني أذهب!
Man Li!
مان لي!
I'm not Man Li!
أنا لست مان لي!
I'm Zhen Yi.
أنا تشن يي.
The daughter of Zhen Huai'an.
ابنة تشن هوايان.
How could you be
كيف يمكن أن تكون
the daughter of Zhen Huai'an?
ابنة تشن هوايان؟
Why not?
ولم لا؟
Why can't I be the daughter of Zhen Huai'an?
لماذا لا أستطيع أن أكون ابنة تشن هوايان؟
Man Li,
مان لي,
you know
أنت تعرف
I have my own reasons too.
لدي أسبابي الخاصة أيضاً.
For the sake of the bond we shared,
من أجل الرابطة التي تقاسمناها،
please let me go, okay?
من فضلك دعني أذهب، حسنًا؟
Man Li,
مان لي,
if you let me go now,
إذا سمحت لي بالذهاب الآن،
I will kneel to your parents and admit my faults, alright?
سأركع أمام والديك وأعترف بأخطائي، حسنًا؟
I'm sorry!
أنا آسف!
Man Li, please forgive me!
مان لي، من فضلك سامحني!
Sister!
أخت!
Man Li.
مان لي.
Zhenyao. You came at the right time. Quick.
زينياو. لقد أتيتَ في الوقت المناسب. بسرعة.
Give it to me.
أعطيني إياه.
Yao.
لهم.
You're back.
لقد عدت.
Carry on.
حمل.
I have work to do.
لدي عمل يجب أن أقوم به.
Hold on.
يتمسك.
Come here.
تعال الى هنا.
Yao.
لهم.
Will you do it yourself,
هل ستفعل ذلك بنفسك؟
or do you want me to help you?
أم تريدني أن أساعدك؟
I...
أنا...
I'll do it myself.
سأفعل ذلك بنفسي.
Luo Zhenyao, go to hell.
لوه تشن ياو، اذهب إلى الجحيم.
Yao.
لهم.
It's a misunderstanding.
إنه سوء فهم.
A misunderstanding.
سوء فهم.
Hey, Yao.
مهلا ياو.
Don't...
لا...
It's a misunderstanding.
إنه سوء فهم.
Yao.
لهم.
Please.
لو سمحت.
From this moment on, the North City Chamber of Commerce
من هذه اللحظة فصاعدا، غرفة تجارة مدينة الشمال
belongs to me.
إنها ملك لي.
It's mine!
إنها لي!
Sister...
أخت...
Xu?
شو؟
Xu!
شو!
Everyone, come out!
الجميع، يخرجون!
Zhou Musheng.
تشو موشينغ.
You betrayed the entire North City Chamber of Commerce.
لقد خنت غرفة التجارة في مدينة الشمال بأكملها.
Heed my order!
إستمع لطلبي!
Search the city and capture Zhou Musheng.
ابحث عن المدينة وألقي القبض على تشو موشينغ.
- Yes.
- نعم.
♪The world all marvels as fireworks rise♪
♪يندهش العالم كله عندما ترتفع الألعاب النارية♪
♪Magnificent like a blooming dream♪
♪رائعة مثل حلم مزدهر♪
♪Yet who sees the lingering red after the burst♪
♪ومع ذلك من يرى اللون الأحمر المتبقي بعد الانفجار♪
♪Fading into the cold night sky♪
♪تتلاشى في سماء الليل الباردة♪
♪Without the graves of blood and fire♪
♪بدون قبور الدم والنار♪
♪How could there be glory in prosperous times♪
♪كيف يمكن أن يكون هناك مجد في الأوقات المزدهرة♪
♪May that fleeting red of fireworks remain in our hearts♪
♪أتمنى أن يبقى ذلك اللون الأحمر العابر للألعاب النارية في قلوبنا♪
♪Freedom and faith engraved forever♪
♪الحرية والإيمان محفوران إلى الأبد♪
♪You and I are both in the muddy flood♪
♪أنت وأنا في الطوفان الموحل♪
♪Destined to share life and death together♪
♪مُقدَّر لنا أن نتقاسم الحياة والموت معًا♪
♪Life lights the night sky like fireworks' red♪
♪الحياة تضيء سماء الليل مثل الألعاب النارية الحمراء♪
♪Not seeking to engulf the world, just refusing mediocrity♪
♪لا أسعى إلى ابتلاع العالم، فقط أرفض الرداءة♪
♪Even if a single second is all we have in life♪
♪حتى لو كانت ثانية واحدة هي كل ما لدينا في الحياة♪
♪We must sow seeds for our ideals♪
♪علينا أن نزرع بذورًا لمُثُلنا العليا♪